André Pilt Olsen

Jurist hos M.J. ERIKSSON A/S | Construction lawyer Copenhagen, Capital Region, Denmark

Summary

Experienced legal adviser with a demonstrated history of working in the transportation/trucking/railroad industry. Skilled in International Law, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Word, Procurement, and Company Law. Strong operations professional with a Master of Laws, cand. jur. focused in Law from Københavns Universitet / University of Copenhagen.



Experience

M.J. ERIKSSON A/S

Jurist

February 2021 - Present (2 years 5 months)

København og omegn

Banedanmark

Contract Manager

May 2017 - February 2021 (3 years 10 months)

Amerika Plads 15, 2100 København Ø

Contract management and construction law

COWI

Legal specialist

January 2016 - April 2017 (1 year 4 months)

Copenhagen Area, Denmark

Advising on tenders, contract preparation, contract management and construction law

SIRIUS advokater

4 years

Advokat / Attorney-at-law

February 2014 - December 2015 (1 year 11 months)

Copenhagen Area, Denmark

Specialiseret i selskabsret, virksomhedsoverdragelse, generel erhvervsret, entrepriseret, kontrakter samt fast ejendom, herunder erhvervslejeret. Advokatfuldmægtig / assistant attorney January 2012 - January 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Specialiseret i selskabsret, virksomhedsoverdragelse, generel erhvervsret, entrepriseret og kontrakter.

University of Copenhagen
Undervisningsassistent i obligationsret
February 2012 - November 2014 (2 years 10 months)

Kromann Reumert
Advokatfuldmægtig / assistant attorney
February 2011 - December 2011 (11 months)

Arbejdsområdet var primært generel erhvervs- og selskabsret, samt virksomhedsoverdragelse.

University of Copenhagen
2 years 5 months
Stud. jur. FOCOFIMA
April 2010 - January 2011 (10 months)

SG-leder September 2008 - December 2010 (2 years 4 months)

A4 advokatfirma Stud. jur. January 2008 - December 2008 (1 year)

Lån & Spar Bank Stud. jur. January 2007 - December 2007 (1 year)

Education

Københavns Universitet / University of Copenhagen Master of Laws, cand. jur., Law · (2005 - 2011)

The University of Western Australia Exchange student, Law (2009 - 2009)

Nykøbing Katedralskole

Matematisk student, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates · (2000 - 2003)

Activity

06/02/2023, Jakob Torring added candidate to General Legal Counsel in Copenhagen Area